The Clover Kingdom.
In this place where magic is everything,
there lives one boy who was born without it.
His name is Asta.
His strength and determination helped him become a magic knight.
And despite the many challenges he faces,
he aims for the top and refuses to give up.
Rich or poor, royalty or commoner,
Asta believes anyone can shine.
His mission is to prove that to the whole world,
and to become the next Wizard King.
It's also a special cheer work with Liu contract.
My wife, thanks for the malfunction.
There are many,
I always have vision,
but it helps you come.
It's Wiring,
and I don't think so what's happening,
but the magic ofondo.
This year,
when I drove,
Not exactly what I can do
Don't want a star
Go, no, no, no
You're so on
Me like this
I'm gonna get on
You shine like a diamond
The Magic Knights
Nine squads of capable mages
Who specialize in combat spells
In direct service to the Wizard King
These heroes dedicate their lives to protecting the kingdom
It is said that a Magic Knight squad captain possesses the strength and prowess of a hundred mages combined
Along with the Wizard King
The captains are revered as great role models
Recently, these Titans went head-to-head in a mock tournament organized by Sir Julius
Who sought to bolster the fighting spirit of the Magic Knight squads before their next major battle
Dark magic
Dark course
Yoo-hoo!
I used my dream magic to transport you to Glamour World
I guess I'll have to take a direct approach
It's more my style anyway
Now, Dark Cloak
Light the Slash
Mercury Magic
Silver Shining Regal Sphere
Can you move?
Who do you think you're talking to, Royal Boy?
Let's end this fight
Now
I don't take orders from snobs like you!
Hold nothing back!
I don't think so
Then whatever plan you may have
It'll turn to ash along with you
As a royal who guards this kingdom
And as captain of the Silver Eagles
I refuse to be defeated in such a pathetic manner
I'm sure you're watching, Crimson Lion Kings
Remember there is nothing our passionate flames cannot incinerate
I'll show you the spell I used a while back
A time when I really pushed past my limits
Monosome
Dark Cloak
Dimension
Slash
One-off!
That day
Asta and the rest of the Magic Knights
Renewed their promise to guard the Clover Kingdom
From the looming threat posed by the Spade Kingdom
And the Devil Magikula
Which meant that they would need to become stronger than ever before
Water creation magic!
Sea Dragon's roar!
For months, each of the nine Magic Knight squads worked hard to hone their skills
So they'd be ready to face this fearsome new enemy
Asta and Noel were especially inspired by the captain's tournament and strove to increase their power
Knowing that their crucial meeting with the Heart Kingdom's spirit guardians was fast approaching
Hey Asta! Noel!
Noelle!
We better head out!
Sweet!
Let's go!
Is it time already?
Ooh, an outing with my friends! My heart is leaping with joy! It makes me want to do a little happy dance!
Hm?
Right!
Vimeo
Uh, huh
It makes me wanna do a little happy dance!
Hm?
Right!
That's a good sign.
The town's mostly recovered from the Eye of the Midnight Sun's attack.
Wow, Captain! Thank you so much for inviting us on this trip with you!
Well, I could let you tag along so you'd finally shut up and give me a little peace, but sure, you're welcome.
I had to come back to where it all started!
Today makes one whole year. It's not hard to believe it's been that long, but part of me feels like it flew right by.
This momentous day marks the annual Magic Knight's entrance exam, which is held in the Colosseum.
Good luck on the exam!
Remember, you're the stars of this kingdom!
Our future's in your hands, so try to make us proud!
Since parts of the nation are still rebuilding from the Eye of the Midnight Sun's rampage,
there are fewer applicants now than in years prior.
All right, you're free to watch, but don't go sticking your nose into it.
Yes, sir!
You can trust us.
Can you believe it? That was us just a year ago.
Anybody in this crowd could become our newest member.
I want to be more like you, Miss Noelle! Teach me how!
Having someone look up to me like that might be kind of nice.
Asta! Heads up!
What the heck is the deal with all these weird birds?
Hey, I think those are anti-birds, right?
The ones that like to pick up people who don't possess much mana?
Leave me alone, you stupid things!
Cut it out! Can't you ever give a guy a break?
The way they're swarming him must have zero mana.
Guess someone always has it worse.
He literally just got here.
Noelle.
Hi, Nozel!
So you're here too?
Yeah, it was that dummy.
Er, I mean, Asta's idea.
Before we fight Spade,
he thought that it might help if we could revisit our roots
and look back on how we both became Magic Knights.
So it's been a year, has it?
Right.
What are you doing?
I just...
Right.
What are you doing?
I just...
Don't play dumb with me.
I've told you royalty need not undergo the same tests as common folk.
Yes, but...
Enough.
Where you'll go is already decided.
Stop this pointless nonsense.
Yes.
Of course, Nozel.
Although, if we're being honest,
your very existence is pointless.
I get it now, though.
My brother did all that out of kindness,
because he didn't want me to have to go into battle.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
It's just...
A year ago, when I got my squat assignment,
I couldn't help but wonder why I ended up in the Black Bulls.
But later,
I realized that it was actually a perfect fit for me.
So now I'm grateful to you.
The people I work with,
they're like my family.
I've shared experiences with them
that I wouldn't trade for anything.
You've grown, Noelle.
I'm proud.
Thank you so much.
I know you have the potential to grow even more
and to become a better mage.
Yes.
Just like our mother.
I told you guys to buzz off!
Everybody knows I don't have magic,
so let's move on already!
I don't know.
The Magic Knight captains are here.
They're kind of overwhelming, huh?
I am the captain of the Golden Dawn, William Vonges.
I'll be conducting the Magic Knight's entrance exam today.
First of all, I'd like to commend you for participating.
After the havoc caused by the Eye of the Midnight Sun, the Clover Kingdom needs its
mages more than ever.
That's Lord Vonges, the famous hero!
He's praising us!
And of course, you must know this.
Even if you fail today, your journey isn't over.
Anyone is free to retake the exam as many times as they desire.
With that said, Magic Tree, Descent!
The Magic Knight's entrance exam will now commence.
Man!
This sure takes me back!
Yeah, same here.
You couldn't even get off the ground, remember?
Huh?
You were watching me?
Well, it was kind of hard not to.
You stuck out like a sore thumb.
Not only that, but you had no magic power.
I thought for sure you'd fail spectacularly.
But to everyone's surprise...
You know, kid, I like you.
Come join our crew.
What?
Quit gaping like a fish.
I'm saying I'll let you into the Black Bulls.
Captain Yami took a liking to you.
And since then...
No matter how severely you got hurt...
You never gave up.
No matter how many times you fell...
You always...
Always...
Got back on your feet.
Right here.
Right now!
I'm going to push past my limits!
Whatever comes at you, you fight your way through it.
You're truly incredible.
But only a little bit!
Thanks a lot, Noelle!
You're pretty awesome yourself!
You've got a crazy amount of mana.
And you keep on learning how to use better and better techniques.
Your water clothes are super cool, too!
It's got a name, you idiot!
It's called Valkyrie Armor!
Yeah, that!
You knew what I was talking about!
Anyway, you rock!
Well, no need to make such a fuzz.
We've really been through a lot of challenges, though, haven't we?
True.
And I'm sure, in the future, we'll face even greater obstacles.
Things that we can't even imagine yet.
Don't you think?
Yeah, good thing we have the Captains!
And all the other Magic Knights!
Plus, we're tougher now.
We're gonna put our skills together and protect the Clover Kingdom!
No matter what it takes!
Let's become stronger!
Oh yeah, way stronger.
I'm sorry, what's so interesting about this exam?
I see, you're too cool to respond.
Asta, wait up!
Where are you going?
Hey, you know!
Where ain't this guy again?
You're here too, huh?
I know you're Mr. Cool and everything, but you can't just walk by me without saying hello first.
Meh.
Wait!
Did you just say meh?!
Who does that?!
You think you're so great!
He doesn't think he knows!
Are you kidding me?!
He's not cool at all!
He's only trying to be cool!
What do you mean by trying?
You know doesn't need to try to be cool.
Cause it comes naturally for him, dork!
Well anyway, if you came here, then I guess you're thinking about our promise.
What promise?
That someday, I'll be the Wizard King!
Like you could!
Well, not just me!
I...
I'm never going to cry again!
I've decided!
What do you mean?
I'll do it too!
I'm going to become the Wizard King!
I'll work hard and get strong so I can protect you and everybody else!
I'll do whatever it takes!
And I'll never give up!
I'll never give up!
We'll fight to see who will be the Wizard King!
Whatever it takes!
Okay, but it's still gonna be me.
Nah, the title's mine and you know it is!
It's mine for sure!
Nuh-uh!
So...
You rookies feel like you got back to your roots or whatever?
Yeah, it was awesome!
Thank you!
Yes.
Alright.
I'm feeling more motivated now as well.
I swear, I'll strengthen my magic and fortify my bonds with friends.
Same here!
I'll give it my all!
And help to make the Black Bulls the greatest team ever!
Also, I'll break my curse and prove I'm worthy of Lady Phineas' hand!
Let's do our best, guys!
By the way, Captain, did we recruit any new people?
Am I taking on a protege?
There was one that I kinda liked.
But then another squad snapped him up.
Which means you two have to stay at the bottom for at least another whole year.
Come on, let's go.
I knew I'd find you here.
Ah, hello, Marks. This is a coincidence.
I don't see what's so coincidental about you sneaking out of the castle yet again.
We should get back. Your work is constantly piling up.
I'm well aware. You know?
Yes?
It's inspiring to see this many young people building their skills so they can join the Magic Knights and protect our land.
That's why I wanted to come here. The sight of it is extremely encouraging to me.
Yes, you're right. They give us hope, don't they?
Now then, shall we depart?
I've been meaning to ask you, Marks, do you enjoy eating grilled violet snake?
Is that a real question?
If you do, I was thinking I could catch one and cook it for you soon.
That won't be necessary, sir.
Aw, I bet Asta would be more than happy to have some.
Yuno.
I have something for you.
What is it?
It's my old pendant.
But how?
A man named Revchi brought it.
Is that true?
From what I understand, it was one of the many valuable artifacts that he and Gelder took when they robbed the Shadow Palace.
He was probably afraid of what you would do to him if you ever discovered that he had it, so he thought it wise to return it.
I'm relieved to know that your magic stone is back in your hands.
Me too.
I never expected he'd be the one to return it to me.
Strange.
I'm so happy for you.
Today marks one year.
You've been an irreplaceable asset.
I'm grateful.
Make me proud, you know.
Now then, everyone's waiting.
Let's go.
All right, you ready?
For more training?
Heck yeah!
Are you crazy?
No, we're partying tonight.
Partying?
Yeah, it's the one year anniversary of you two joining the squad.
There's a lot going on right now.
But we wanted to do something for you at least.
Magna and the others should be back soon too.
Thank you guys!
I guess I'll let you celebrate me if you want to.
Okay.
Just for tonight, let's all forget about fighting and really let loose.
Yes, sir!
It's time to have some fun.
A whole night of bonding with my best friends.
Knock knock!
Hey Charmy, we're back!
I've gotten a lot stronger in the past year.
Now.
Better keep going.
I'll keep reaching greater heights until I become the Wizard King.
I'll work as hard as I can.
And one day, I'll be the next Wizard King.
At least you want to feel free.
Thank you for listening.
Thank you.
まだ消せない誓い叫んでる 忘れないように叫んでる
泣きたいほど遠くだって 全然届かなくても
信じる君は赤い手前を向いている
だから枯れないように柄がって 描いた夢また歩き出せる
きっと僕を呼ぶ声だ
ご視聴ありがとうございました